Guide to the Russell Van Nest Black papers, 1919-1968.
Black, Russell Van Nest papers
- Series IV. Subject Files
  - L - M
    - Land Economics, 1932-1947, 1960-1967 (Box 33, Folder 3)
      Subject and/or Publication: Detroit, Michigan. Land Use Economics. Jurkat, Ernest - "Land Use Analysis and Forecasting in Traffic Planning"; American Society of Planning Officials - "A Program for the Use of Tax - Abandoned Lands", Chicago, 1942; Buttenheim, Harold - "Possible Modifications of Urban Land Politics in America"; Pickard, Jerome - Changing Urban Land Uses as Affected by Taxation, 1962.
    - Land Platting, September 1938 (Box 48, Folder 3)
      Subject and/or Publication: "Report of the Committee on Land Subdivision Manual"
    - Landscape Design, 1913-1966 (Box 33, Folder 4)
      Subject and/or Publication: Memphis, Tennessee; Reading, Pennsylvania; Middletown, New Jersey. Building Setback Lines. Landscape Architecture.
    - Maps and Mappings, 1935-1961 (Box 33, Folder 5)
      Subject and/or Publication: Black, Russell - "Tentative Draft of Survey Outlines," for Manual of Planning Surveys; Comey, Arthur; McNamara, Katherine - "State and National Planning: An Analysis of the Subject Arranged With Particular Reference to the Classification of Library Material";Pray, James; Kimball, Theodora - "City Planning: A Comprehensive Analysis of the Subject Arranged for the Classification of Books, Plans, Photographs, Notes and Other Collected Material"; Kimbal Theodora - "Classified Selected List of References on City Planning"; Person, H. S. - "Little Waters: AStudy of Headwater Streams and Other Little Waters, Their Use and Relations to the Land" 1936; Black and Russell - "The Landscape Architect and Planning," 1960; Tibbitts, Armand - "A Terrace Gardent by the Sea".
    - Minutes of the City Planning Society, 1924-1925 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Model City Planning Ordinances - New Jersey, 1926-1940 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - N-Parks, Parkways and Playgrounds
    - Parks and Playgrounds, 1913-1958 (Box 34, Folder 6)
      Subject and/or Publication: Playground Planning - Highway Planning - Sacramento, California; Cleveland, Ohio; New Jersey; Connecticut; London. Olmstead, Frederick Lane - "Report of State Park Survey of California"; Unwin, Raymond - "Interim Report on Decentralization", London; Unwin, Raymond - "Interim Report on Open Spaces"; Knapp, Drewett & Sons. Holleran, Leslie; Clarke, Gilmore - "Parks and Parkways", NY.
    - Parks and Playgrounds, 1913-1958 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Programs and Papers (ASLA, ASCE, Institute and Conference), 1925, 1959 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Public Buildings and Institutions, 1922-1957 (Box 35, Folder 3)
      Subject and/or Publication: Chicago; U.S.. Building Public, Schools.
    - Public Works Programing, 1941-1948, 1969 (Box 35, Folder 4)
      Subject and/or Publication: Public Works; Moses, Robert - "On A Public Works Reservoir," January 8, 1942; Housing - U.S.A.
    - Publication and Education, 1920-1969 (Box 35, Folder 5)
      Subject and/or Publication: Buffalo, New York; Akron, Ohio.Adams, Ferderick - "Urban Planning Education in the U.S.," Ohio; Branch, Melville C. - "Urban Planning and Public Opinion: National Survey Research Investigation, New Jersey.
  - PL - PR
    - Planning Education, 1927-1966 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Planning and Plant Material, 1912-1948 (Box 35, Folder 7)
      Subject and/or Contents: Landscape Architecture Books
    - Population, 1921-1967 (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Ports and Harbors, 1950 (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Post-War Planning, 1932, 1941-1944, 1969 (Box 35, Folder 10)
      Subject and/or Publication: Roads; Military; Moses, Robert - "Parks, Parkways, Express Arteries, and Related Plans for N.Y. City After the War," American City, December 1942. Great Britain; United States of America; Toledo, Ohio; London.
    - Professional Societies- Codes, Charges, Memberships, 1924-1969 (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - Professional Societies- Codes, Charges, Memberships, 1924-1969 (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - Programs and Papers, 1928-1937 (Box 48, Folder 3)
      Subject and/or Publication: "Proceedings of the Second Annual State-Wide Planning Conference of the New Jersey State Planning Board"; "Joint Planning Conference of the American Society of Planning Officials"; "Practical City Planning in Pennsylvania" by the Pennsylvania Association of Planning Commissioners
    - Publicity and Education, 1936 (Box 48, Folder 3)
      Subject and/or Publication: American Society of Planning Officials Newsletter
  - R - Transportation
    - Regional Planning: San Francisco, pamphlets, 1923-1925 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - Regional Planning, 1923-1925 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Regional Planning, 1920-1967 (Box 36, Folder 2)
      Subject and/or Publication: Regional Planning - Metropolitan Planning - Black, Russell - "Joint Planning Board Aids Orderly Development," American City (February 1952); Bartholomew, Harland - "The Present and Ultimate Effect of Decentralization Upon American Cities," Chicago: Urban Land Institute; Comey, Arthur - "Regional Planning Theory: A Reply to the British Challenge," 1923; Mumford, Lewis - "Regional Planning in the Pacific Northwest", Oregon 1939; Comey, Arthur - "Development of the Regional Plan for New England," Preliminary Draft. Boston; National Resources Board. 1942
    - School Facilities and School Buildings., 1916-1945 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Shopping Centers, 1934-1959 (Box 36, Folder 4)
      Subject and/or Publication: Stein, Clarence, Bauer, Catherine - "Store Buildings and Neighborhood Shopping Centers," Architectural Record (February 1934)
    - Special Topics - Nuisances (Billboards), 1908-1950 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Standards, 1917-1960 (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - State and County Planning, 1935-1953 (Box 36, Folder 7)
      Subject and/or Publication: County Planning - State Planning - Bucks County, Pennsylvania; New Jersey; Los Angeles, California.
    - Street Design, 1945-1953 (Box 36, Folder 8)
      Subject and/or Contents: Highways; Roads - Improvement.
    - Surveys, 1924-1964 (Box 36, Folder 9-10)
    - Traffic and Safety, 1925-1946 (Box 36, Folder 11)
    - Transportation, 1922-1966 (Box 37, Folder 1)
      Subject and/or Contents: City Transportation; Railroads; Traffic Engineering; Highways.
  - U - Zoning Ordinances
    - Urban Redevelopment, 1943-1968 (Box 37, Folder 2)
      Subject and/or Publication: Urban Renewal; Buttenheim, Harold - Know Your City - The Economic Values Attendant Upon the Replanning of Blighted Areas, Philadelphia: Housing Association, 1930
    - Urban Standards, 1950-1951 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Utilities, 1928-1968 (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Water Supply and Sewage Disposal, 1920-1959 (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Zoning Ordinances (Areas in Which RVNB Served), undated (Box 37, Folder 6-7)
      Subject and/or Publication: New Jersey; Pennsylvania; New York. Multiple Municipalities. Zoning Ordinances; Zoning Maps.
    - Zoning Ordinances (Black's Name is on Report), undated (Box 37, Folder 8)
      Subject and/or Publication: New Jersey; Pennsylvania; North Carolina; New York. Multiple Municipalities. Zoning Ordinances; Zoning Maps.
    - Zoning Ordinances, undated (Box 38, Folder 1)
      Subject and/or Publication: Nebraska; Ohio; California; Wisconsin; Florida; South Carolina; Oregon; Tennessee; Black, Russell - "Why so Much Zoning and so Little Planning" 1951; Bartholomew, Harland - "How Much Commercial Area Should be Provided for in Zoning Ordinances,"; Adams, Frederick - "Density Standards for Multi-family Residential Areas," 1943, Bettman, Alfred - "General Scope of Function of Zoning Board of Appeals," 1929. Zoning Standards; Zoning Maps; Zoning Ordinances.
    - Zoning Administration Forms, undated (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Zoning Data, 1919-1968 (Box 38, Folder 3-7)
      Subject and/or Publication: Buttenheim, Harold - "Standards for Garden Apartments," American City (December 1950); Reps, John - "Practical Aids to Better Zoning Administration," American City (September 1947). Legal Notices, Clippings, Articles, Reports.
    - Zoning- New Clauses, 1952-1965 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Zoning: Trial Notices, Clippings
    - A-F
      - Accessory Uses, 1951 (Box 38, Folder 9)
      - Administrative Procedure (Other than Board of Appeals), undated (Box 38, Folder 10)
      - Advertising, Outdoors, 1943, 1948, 1949 (Box 38, Folder 11)
      - Aesthetics, 1938, 1949, 1955 (Box 38, Folder 12)
      - Airport Zoning, 1945-1946 (Box 38, Folder 13)
      - Amendment, 1945 (Box 38, Folder 14)
      - American City- Zoning and Planning Decisions (Mostly in the 1930's), 1930's (Box 38, Folder 15)
      - Untitled, 1953, 1955, 1962 (Box 38, Folder 16)
      - Billboards (See Advertising - Outdoor), 1945, 1953 (Box 38, Folder 17)
      - Board of Appeals- Appeal, undated (Box 38, Folder 18)
      - Board of Appeals- Applications to, undated (Box 38, Folder 19)
      - Board of Appeals (Exercise of Discretionary Powers), 1950 (Box 38, Folder 20)
      - Board of Appeals (Exercise of General Powers), 1945, 1949, 1951 (Box 38, Folder 21)
      - Board of Appeals - Review by Courts of Decision, undated (Box 38, Folder 22)
      - Board of Appeals- Variance, 1946 (Box 38, Folder 23)
      - Building Lines- Mapped Streets, 1929, 1944, 1948 (Box 38, Folder 24)
        Subject and/or Publication: Black, Mary - "Building Line Legislation". Chicago Regional Planning Association.
      - Business District, 1950, 1953 (Box 38, Folder 25)
      - Change from Lower to higher Classification, undated (Box 38, Folder 26)
      - Comprehensive City Plan (Element in Court Decision), 1948 (Box 38, Folder 27)
      - Conflicting Jurisdiction- Municipal, State, Federal and Inter-Municipal, 1956 (Box 38, Folder 28)
      - Consent- Property Owners, 1953 (Box 38, Folder 29)
        Subject and/or Contents: Example Cases Where Property Rights were Upheld Against Government Zoning Regulations.
      - Consent, Public Authorities, undated (Box 38, Folder 30)
        Subject and/or Contents: North Hills, New York. Zoning. Re: Kelley v. Levitt and Sons, Inc.;American Society of Planning Officials Newsletter.
      - Constitutionality, 1948 (Box 38, Folder 31)
        Subject and/or Publication: Bassett, Edward - "No City Issues Zoning Bonds," (March 1948)
      - County and Rural Zoning, undated (Box 38, Folder 32)
      - Definitions, undated (Box 38, Folder 33)
      - Density of Population, 1941, 1953 (Box 38, Folder 34)
        Subject and/or Publication: Density of Population; Bassett, Edward - "One-Family Dwellings and Density of Population Under Zoning," American City (January 1941.) p. 103.
      - District Boundary Lines (Validity of), undated (Box 38, Folder 35)
      - Eminent Domain- Zoning, undated (Box 38, Folder 36)
      - Faulty Ordinances (Including Unreasonable), undated (Box 38, Folder 37)
      - Financial Advantages of Appellant (A Factor in Decision), 1946, 1948 (Box 38, Folder 38)
      - Flood Protection Zoning, undated (Box 38, Folder 39)
      - Front Yards, 1955 (Box 38, Folder 40)
    - G-V
      - Garage, undated (Box 39, Folder 1)
      - Garden Apartments, 1946, 1952 (Box 39, Folder 2)
      - Height of Buildings, undated (Box 39, Folder 3)
      - Highway Zoning, undated (Box 39, Folder 4)
      - Home Rule, undated (Box 39, Folder 5)
      - Housing (Including Redevelopment Plans), 1950, 1952 (Box 39, Folder 6)
      - Industrial District, 1950, 1955 (Box 39, Folder 7)
      - Interim, Pending or Partial Ordinance, 1947 (Box 39, Folder 8)
      - Laches, undated (Box 39, Folder 9)
      - Land Subdivision Regulation, 1944, 1950 (Box 39, Folder 10)
      - Land Under Water, undated (Box 39, Folder 11)
      - Legislature and Courts, 1952 (Box 39, Folder 12)
      - Lot Area Per Dwelling Unit (Includes lot Dimension), 1950, 1954 (Box 39, Folder 13)
      - Master Plan- An Encumbrance, 1941, 1942, 1948 (Box 39, Folder 14)
        Master Plan; Black, Russell - "A Planning Consultant's Opinion," American City (September 1942). es.
      - Mechanics Liens, undated (Box 39, Folder 15)
      - Medium Size of Dwelling (Includes Cost Provisions), 1951, 1952 (Box 39, Folder 16)
      - Nuisances, undated (Box 39, Folder 17)
      - Parking- Off Street, 1943, 1946, 1950, 1956 (Box 39, Folder 18)
      - Pending Zoning Ordinances or Amendment (Cessom. For not Issuing Permits), undated (Box 39, Folder 19)
      - Permits, undated (Box 39, Folder 20)
      - Need of Plan, Zone, undated (Box 39, Folder 21)
      - Planning Board- Power- General, 1931, 1938 (Box 39, Folder 22)
      - Private Restrictions, 1947-1948 (Box 39, Folder 23)
      - Procedural Errors and Omissions, 1944, 1952-1953 (Box 39, Folder 24)
      - Public Property, undated (Box 39, Folder 25)
      - Publication of Ordinance and Map, undated (Box 39, Folder 26)
      - Racial Zoning, 1950 (Box 39, Folder 27)
      - Reasonable (Ordinance Must Be), undated (Box 39, Folder 28)
      - Removal of Soil and Minerals, 1950, 1953 (Box 39, Folder 29)
      - Residential Districts, 1945-1954 (Box 39, Folder 30)
      - Residential Districts Agriculture, 1944-1947 (Box 39, Folder 31)
      - Side Yards, undated (Box 39, Folder 32)
      - Special or Unusual Provisions, 1943-1953 (Box 39, Folder 33)
      - Spot Zoning, 1948-1954 (Box 39, Folder 34)
      - Streets (Mostly Non-Zoning Cases), 1949 (Box 39, Folder 35)
      - Trailer Camps, 1935, 1946 (Box 39, Folder 36)
      - Unnecessary Hardship (See Board of Appeals- Variance), undated (Box 39, Folder 37)
      - Use- Non-conforming (Continuance) and Extension, 1948, 1951, 1955 (Box 39, Folder 38)
      - Use Provisions Validity, 1945-1949 (Box 39, Folder 39)
      - Use Provisions, Violation of, 1950 (Box 39, Folder 40)
      - Use- Within Specified Distance of and the Use, 1948 (Box 39, Folder 41)
      - Uses- Excluded from District or City, 1949, 1951 (Box 39, Folder 42)
      - Uses- Non-Conforming (Vacation Thereof), 1950, 1955 (Box 39, Folder 43)
      - Value, 1945 (Box 39, Folder 44)
      - Variances vs. Changes, undated (Box 39, Folder 45)
      - Vested Interest- Acquired- or Not in Light to Violate- Use Provisions for Various Reasons, 1946 (Box 39, Folder 46)
    - Unsorted
      - Appendix to Brief for Appellant, 1954-1955 (Box 46, Folder 15)
        Court Case: Clary, Edmund B., Black Russell. Borough of Education
      - Two Books of Slides, undated (Box 46, Folder 16-17)
      - Planning Education Box 17, 1936-1941 (Box 47, Folder 1)
        Conference on Planning. Black, Russell, V.N.; Massachusetts Institute of Technology.
      - Clary vs. Eatontown, 1956 (Box 47, Folder 2)
        Photostat Record. Opinion. Borough of Education; Black, Russell, V.N.
      - Bacon, Edmund M., Sert, Josehius; Black Russell, V.N.; Harvard University., 1956 (Box 47, Folder 3)
      - Hoyt Homer. Chicago Planning Commission, Urban Land Institute, American Institute of Planners, 1944-1955 (Box 47, Folder 4)
      - Lewis, Harold M. Gibson, J.E., 1922-1937 (Box 47, Folder 5)
      - Bettman, Alfred. Urban Redevelopment Legislation., 1944 (Box 47, Folder 6)
      - D - File, 1947 (Box 47, Folder 7)
        D and W Blueprint Co. Russell VN Black
      - E - File, 1946 (Box 47, Folder 8)
        Ideological Difference. Black, Russell V.N., Ely, George H.
      - Edgewater, New Jersey. Zoning, 1934 (Box 47, Folder 9)
      - Livingston Township, 1947 (Box 47, Folder 10)
      - Maling List Changes and Additions, 1929-1937 (Box 47, Folder 11)
        Addresses of Planning Boards, City Planner.
      - O Prospects, 1940-1941 (Box 47, Folder 12)
        Planning Board of the City of Orange
      - Pennsylvania State Planning Board, 1935-1936 (Box 47, Folder 13)
        National Resources Committee, Pennsylvania State Planning Board.
      - Substistence Homesteads, undated (Box 47, Folder 14)
      - National Planning Board, 1939 (Box 47, Folder 15)
        Local City Planning
      - Personal, 1892-1967 (Box 47, Folder 16)
      - Correspondence, 1934 (Box 47, Folder 17)
      - Ordinance, 1939 (Box 47, Folder 18)
      - United States Department of the Interior National Park Service Pamphlets, undated (Box 47, Folder 19)
- Series V. Russell Black Consulting Reports
  Arranged first alphabetically by location and then chronologically
  - A-L (arranged by date, 1921-1967)
    - "Final Report of Studies and Recommendations for the New Town of American Falls, Idaho", September 29, 1921 (Box 39, Folder 47)
      Subject and/or Contents: Regarding Hightstown, New Jersey
    - "Town Planning and Preliminary Draft of a Zoning Ordinance for Hightstown, New Jersey", May 1, 1922 (Box 39, Folder 48)
    - "The Hightstown Town Plan", May 15, 1922 (Box 39, Folder 49)
    - "Parks and Playgrounds for Palo Alto, California", December 1923 (Box 39, Folder 50)
    - "A Report of Studies and Recommendations for a Street and Zone Plan for the City of San Buenaventura, California", March 6, 1924 (Box 39, Folder 51)
    - Santa Clara Reports, 1925 (Box 39, Folder 52)
      Subject and/or Contents: "Plan of Santa Clara- The Heart of Santa Clara Valley."Santa Clara, California. 1925; "A Report of Recommendations for the Development and Improvement of Santa Clara, California" Santa Clara, California. June 9, 1925
    - "A Report on Borough Plan and Revision of Zoning Ordinance- A Supplement to a Comprehensive Plan Report", January 3,1930 (Box 39, Folder 53)
      Subject and/or Contents: Hightstown, New Jersey.
    - "The Bound Brook Plan- A Report Upon a Borough Master Plan and Revision of the Zoning Ordinance", June 1932 (Box 39, Folder 54)
    - "Bound Brook Plan", June 1932 (Box 39, Folder 55)
    - "Report on Revision of Zoning Ordinance and Map for the City of Englewood, New Jersey", July 1933 (Box 39, Folder 56)
    - "Planning and Zoning for the Borough of Edgewater, New Jersey", March 1935 (Box 39, Folder 57)
    - "Island Beach- A Proposal for an Ocean Front Park", June 1937 (Box 39, Folder 58)
    - "The Bridgewater Township Plan- A Report Upon a Master Plan and Zoning Ordinance", September 1937 (Box 39, Folder 59)
    - "A Report Upon City Plan Studies for Long Branch, New Jersey with Special Reverence to Proposed Central-City Street Improvements and Traffic Problems.", 1938 (Box 39, Folder 60)
    - "Recreational Potentialities of Delaware and Raritan Canal Properties for Development Either as a State Park or to Serve the Purpose of Aqueduct Location", June 1940 (Box 39, Folder 61)
    - "A Plan for Franklin Township, Somerset County, New Jersey", June 1940 (Box 39, Folder 62)
    - Planning and Zoning for Township of Chatham, New Jersey,", October 1942 (Box 39, Folder 63)
    - "A Master Plan and Revised Zoning Ordinance for the Borough of Flemington, Hunterdon County, New Jersey", April 1944 (Box 39, Folder 64)
    - "Planning and Zoning for the Township of Livingston, Essex County, New Jersey", July 1946 (Box 39, Folder 65)
    - "Planning and Zoning for the Borough of Highland Park, New Jersey", February 1947 (Box 39, Folder 66)
    - "Zoning for Branchburg Township, Somerset County, New Jersey.", October 1947 (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - "Planning and Zoning for Bernards Township, New Jersey", May 1950 (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - "Planning for the Borough of Edgewater", 1954 (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - "Planning and Zoning for Hamilton Township, Mercer County, New Jersey", May 1956 (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - "Planning and Zoning for the Township of Clinton, Hunterdon County, New Jersey", January 1962 (Box 40, Folder 5-6)
    - Preliminary draft of "Zoning Ordinance for the Township of Clinton, Hunterdon County, New Jersey.", undated (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - "Recreational Potential of Jersey Meadows", undated (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - Industrial Land Use in Burlington County, New Jersey by Breese, Gerald, 1951 (Box 40, Folder 9)
      Subject and/or Contents: Industrial Land Use in Burlington County, New Jersey. A Survey and Analysis of Selected Factors Affecting Existing and Potential Industrial Location Along Major Transportation Routes in the New Jersey Area Between Trenton and Camden. Bureau of Urban Research.
    - Delaware Valley Regional Planning Commission Brochure, 1965-1967 (Box 40, Folder 10)
    - "1965 Regional Planning Projections for the Delaware Valley" DVRPC Plan Report, No 1., 1967 (Box 40, Folder 11)
    - "Steady Growth and Prosperity Forecast for the Delaware Valley" by Heymsfeld, Jeremy., 1967 (Box 40, Folder 12)
    - "Virtually Forgotten 1932 Plan Made Projections Close to Target in 1967" by Frank, Richard., 1967 (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - New Jersey
    - "Park Report for Middlesex County, New Jersey", 1930 (Box 40, Folder 14)
    - "County Plan Report for Mercer County, New Jersey", 1931 (Box 40, Folder 15)
    - "A Master Plan for Mercer County, New Jersey", 1931 (Box 40, Folder 16)
    - Six Months Progress Report Covering Activities of the New Jersey State Planning Board for Period of December 15, 1935- June 15, 1936., 1936 (Box 40, Folder 17-18)
    - "Planning and Zoning for Mount Olive Township, New Jersey", 1937 (Box 40, Folder 19)
    - "A Master Plan for Nutley, New Jersey", 1942 (Box 40, Folder 20)
    - Planning and Zoning for the City of New Brunswick, New Jersey, 1944 (Box 40, Folder 21)
    - "Planning and Zoning for the City of New Brunswick, New Jersey", 1947 (Box 40, Folder 22)
    - "Planning and Zoning for the City of Millville, New Jersey. A Report", 1947 (Box 40, Folder 23)
    - "The Mercer County Plan - 1950. A Guide for the Future Development of Mercer County, New Jersey", 1950 (Box 40, Folder 24)
    - "Rezoning for the Town of Nutley, Essex County, New Jersey", 1953 (Box 40, Folder 25)
    - "Master Plan for Moorestown Township, Burlington County, New Jersey", 1956 (Box 40, Folder 26)
    - "A Digest of the Master Plan for the Township of Moorestown, Burlington County, New Jersey."by Black, Russell and Tokmakian, Harold, 1957 (Box 40, Folder 27)
    - A Parks and Public Lands Plan and Program for New Jersey, 1941 (Box 40, Folder 28)
    - The Proposed New Jersey Cross-State Ship Canal. A Symposium of Fact and Opinion with Special Emphasis Upon State Interests Affected for the Committee on Parks and Public Lands., undated (Box 40, Folder 29)
    - A Preliminary Report Upon Planning Surveys and Planning Studies for the State of New Jersey., 1934 (Box 40, Folder 30)
    - First Annual Report of Progress - A Preliminary Report Upon Planning Surveys and Planning Studies for the State of New Jersey., 1935 (Box 40, Folder 31)
    - The Cost of Government in New Jersey. An Introduction Survey of Public Finance Indicating Where and for What Purpose Public Funds Have Been Spent., 1936 (Box 40, Folder 32)
    - Second Annual Report of Progress. A Preliminary Report Upon Planning Surveys and Planning Studies for the State of New Jersey., 1937 (Box 40, Folder 33)
    - State Planning in New Jersey - What it is, Why is it Needed, How It Operates., 1937 (Box 40, Folder 34)
    - Rural Tax Delinquency in New Jersey, 1929-1934, 1938 (Box 40, Folder 35)
    - Third Annual Report of Progress, 1938 (Box 40, Folder 36)
    - Where Shall we Plan? A Report on the Outdoor Recreational Needs of New Jersey., 1938 (Box 40, Folder 37)
    - Land Subdivision in New Jersey - Its Extent, Quality, and Regulation, 1938 (Box 40, Folder 38)
    - Fourth Annual Report of the New Jersey State Planning Board to the Governor and the Legislature., 1939 (Box 40, Folder 39)
    - Municipal and County Planning Legislation and Procedures in New Jersey, 1939 (Box 40, Folder 40)
    - Fifth Annual Report - New Jersey State Planning Board to the Governor and the Legislature, 1939, 1940 (Box 40, Folder 41)
    - Premature Land Subdivision - A Luxury, 1941 (Box 40, Folder 42)
    - Sixth Annual Report for the Year 1940, 1940 (Box 40, Folder 43)